As you can see, I put a total list for our Chrome extension game and I'll add another prompt.
I want a new feature, a power-ups and start from single double jump.
As you can see, it has been updated how it works, find power-up, look for golden glowing
stars on platforms, collect touch power and collect it, we have a game ability.
So you now have a double jump for the entire game.
There's space twice, once in the ground, I'll just move the screen because I have it
on another account and this is how climb came, well, it works, a press space, yes, I can
jump.
Wow, and we see different type of platforms as well.
It looks great, I see the score at the top left corner, there's a different friction based
on the platform color as well.
And there are some even coins that you can collect.
All right, it's still high score zero and you probably need to add an encounter because
it still has an updated that one, so you probably have to quit or basically lose to get
it registered.
So I'll just add another prompt, great, but make a pick up, a little bit bigger because
the star is so small and probably easier to notice, right?
And we can just quickly add another power up as well, that will probably increase our next
jump.
I think it is a great idea, especially for the type of game, jump height and basically
our added here, so let's make this power bigger and more noticeable and we'll change the
game JavaScript file.
I will skip it for now and go back when it's ready.
Okay, it has been updated, so let's wait for the back, I will re-apolly it on comics
tension.
Okay, I'll just turn it on, as we can see the game is already running, okay, it's possible
to go from one to left and we see already another power up, wow, and the jump is very high,
great, and we can use double jump as you can see, wow, perfect, so we have two types of
power up and possibility to jump and double jump as well, great, let's increase possibility
for that game and power up with increase height, jump should be disappearing.
Because I've noticed one thing, as soon as I have this power up with increase jump, then
you can jump higher, I won't only to be done once, so as soon as we jump high, the power
up with disappear and our no more jumping height will return, but now I'm reloading and
let me try if it actually fixed our issue, hmm, always pretty hard to jump, but it's
possible, so it was my mistake, sorry, see, we had another hard jump, but I was able to do
it, oh, there is a power up, so I'll be able to test it out, and yeah, we see it's for
no better, another power up, one, and we see this one, the second one is smaller, great,
I'll close the window and now I'll go back to the end to do, and we can remove it or
just try to type another instruction for our model, I want you to add a moving mouse on
the platform that we can collect and score points, because we don't have an score system,
so that we'll be displayed, maybe in the hot, okay, I'll pause it and return when it's
ready, it will basically change the game JavaScript file and implement some of the elements,
okay, it's about to finish and we have moving mouse, collecting system, so mouse, spawning
might be running a new platform as we climb, mouse, moving right on the platform, the
same mouse to go, you can get 10 points, points are ready to score in the hot, and plan
your jumps to collect it, all right, I will now turn and open it up, I will reload it,
so I'll just press refresh button, as soon as it refreshed, I will just press start a game
and start it now, great, I found out, I just want to test something, okay, let's go
up now and see if that mouse appears, I will change the possibility to appear more earlier,
but as you can see, we see the shape of the mouse and we see possibilities, okay, this
is 940 and okay, there's a problem with the score, I will go back to our editor, great,
the mouse is smoothing, but I didn't, I don't get any update, right, because we didn't
get any visual update, maybe it started in some variable, it acts below a high score and
we want to make it as two separate variables, so it should probably fix it out, based
on the things, so it will change the composition of the code now, it will add now the
UI function to display the mouse, it's collected and yeah, we see the tracking state
and here I update, so I'll quickly update a game and refresh the CAD clamp game and we
see the mouse collected at the top left corner, so now it's zero and we have a high score
that we probably depend on time and obviously our power ups and basically collection
assistance, so I see the mouse and yeah, that might sparkly this one, the score and the
change, now it's still great, so the score system for the mouse is now working perfectly
flawlessly, right, there are some effects and simple sounds, effects plus music and we
can add whistly possibility to the toggle in the settings, so just add to the prompt simple
sounds, effects plus music, toggle in settings, so SFX which means sound effects, when
we basically overlap with power up, when we collect mouse and when we lose, I look like
a free sound effects and it adds sound system with web audio, APM, it will create power
up collection sound effect, create mouse collection sound effect, game over sound effect
and add a background music, so it added some even additional instructions for it, so it
would take a raw entire sound effect, so I do this, and the sound is playing and we have
been possibility to turn it on, turn it off, there is a baron, let me try and see if we get
some of the sound effects being able up and yeah, I hear it, oh, for this one, it does
more but for mouse, it works, so we probably need to ask about the power ups, get it done,
I will go back to the game, and add another prompt, I will go up, oh, I heard the sound for
both power ups, and for mouse grade, so now we have sound effect side of our main
and get into that comics dash.